One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Rasetsu Prison Flower Capital
سجن ريساتسو عاصمة الزهور
Daddy!
أبي
Smile fruits are more than just artificial devil fruits?
فاكهة "سمايل" أكثر من مجرّد فاكهة شيطان اصطناعيّة؟
Lord Yasuie!
ياسويي-دونو
Tonoyasu...!
...تونوياسو قد
Damn! We're too late!
سُحقًا، تأخّرنا كثيرًا
How did I not recognize him until he was strung up there?!
كيف أمكنني ألاّ أتعرّف عليه إلى أن قُيّد هناك
I should commit seppuku for my blunder...!
...يا حسرتي، حريّ بي أن أنفّذ السّيبّوكو
Lord Yasuie!
ياسويي-ساما
Tonoyasu!
...تونوياسو-سان
He's dead!
لقد مات
Wh-What the hell's this?!
ما-ما الّذي يحدث هنا؟
The Ebisu townspeople adored Tonoyasu.
أحبّه سكّان بلدة إبيسو كثيرًا
Why are they laughing?!
فلماذا يضحكون؟
That bastard Orochi has a twisted sense of humor...
...لدى أوروتشي حسّ دعابة مريض
Prisoner Mining Camp Udon
منجم السجناء أودون
That's one crazy bunch!
لا بدّ أنّهم مجانين
They're laughing at the execution of their former daimyo!
إنّهم يضحكون على إعدام الدّايميو السّابق خاصّتهم
How vicious, Orochi...
أوروتشي قاسي القلب
Sir Yasuie... That was alive until today defies belief...!
ياسويي-دونو... لا أصدّق أنّه كان حيًّا حتّى اليوم
So the enemy knew about the raid we were planning!
إذًا فقد كان يعلم العدوّ بخطّة الغارة الّتي وضعناها
That's why you, Sir Yasuie...
...لهذا السّبب، ياسويي-دونو
put your life on the line...
...ضحّيت بنفسك
to keep our plan alive?!
لإبقاء الخطّة مستمرّة؟
There's gotta be a good reason.
لا بدّ من سبب ما، صحيح؟
No matter who he was...
...لا يهمّ من كان
no one deserves to be laughed at when they die.
...لا يستحقّ أيّ أحد في العالم أن يُضحك عليه
No one!
في لحظة موته
That's probably due to smile fruits.
على الأرجح أنّ "سمايل" هي السّبب
Some of them are in here with us. All they can do is laugh.
يمكن العثور على بعض الّذين لا يسعهم إلاّ الضّحك هنا أيضًا
Bakura Town Kuri
بلدة باكورا كوري
Inuarashi, Kin'emon,
...إينواراشي، كينيمون
do you know about smile fruits?
هل تعرفان بشأن فاكهة "سمايل"؟
I should've told you.
...كان عليَّ إخباركم من قبل
The smiling faces worn by the Ebisu townspeople...
...الوجوه المبتسمة لسكّان بلدة إبيسو
are just masks.
ما هي إلاّ أقنعة
They're wearing masks they can't remove...
...أقنعة لا يمكن نزعها
ever!
لبقيّة حياتهم
A few years ago, Kaido and Orochi...
...قبل بضع سنوات، بدأ كايدو وأوروتشي
started importing some kind of artificial fruit...
باستيراد فاكهة اصطناعيّة من نوع ما
in exchange for the weapons that are made in this country.
مقابل الأسلحة المصنوعة في هذه البلاد
Smile fruits...!
فاكهة "سمايل"؟
Eat one of those dreadful fruits and earn the sea's fury and the inability to swim.
عند أكل المرء لتلك الفاكهة الفظيعة سيكرهه البحر وسيخسر القدرة على السّباحة
In exchange, you gain an animal's power and ferocity.
لكن في المقابل، سيحصل على قدرات حيوان ما وستجعله ضاريًا
Those artificial devil fruits?
إنّها فاكهة شيطان اصطناعيّة، صحيح؟
We destroyed the factory that manufactured them.
دمّرنا المصنع الّذي ينتجها
Indeed... I heard about it from Master Kin...
نعم، أخبرني كين-ساما بذلك
but the country had already seen more than its fair share of the fruit imported.
لكنّ أطنانًا منها سبق ووصلت إلى هذه البلاد
Kaido's aim is to use them to transform his men into ferocious beasts...
هدف كايدو هو جعل أعوانه أقوى كالوحوش الضّارية بتلك الفاكهة
and create the world's most fearsome pirate crew.
وينشئ أعظم طاقم قراصنة في العالم
But there is always a catch when something is too good to be true.
لكن لا يوجد شيء مثالي على أكمل وجه
The success rate for achieving the desired strength enhancement is around 10 percent.
نسبة نجاح تعزيز القوّة الاصطناعيّة هو حوالي 10 في المئة
A mere one in ten of those who eat a smile fruit gains its powers.
إن أكل عشرةٌ الفاكهة، واحد منهم فقط قد يكتسب قدراتها
The other nine are left with no improvements and only the consequences.
أمّا التّسعة الآخرون فلن يلحظوا بأيّ تحسّن وسيواجهون العواقب فحسب
They naturally lose the ability to swim...
وبالطّبع، لن يتمكّنوا من السّباحة ثانية
but as a side effect of these flawed drugs...
وكأعراض جانبيّة للكيماويّات المعيبة
they can no longer express any sadness or anger
لن يعودوا قادرين على التّعبير عن الحزن أو الغضب، سيستطيعون الضّحك فحسب
What?!
ماذا؟
I'm pretty sure Caesar's SAD compound is the active ingredient in those smile fruits!
المكوّن الأساسيّ لـ"سمايل" هو "إس أيْ دي" الّذي كان يصنعه سيزار، صحيح؟
Who knew it had such harmful side effects?
له أعراض جانبيّة فظيعة كهذه؟
Kaido couldn't care less about his crew's safety.
لا يهتمّ كايدو لسلامة أعوانه
All that matters is having powerful soldiers.
يريد جنودًا أقوياء فحسب
The Beast Pirates have three categories of fighters.
المقاتلون في قراصنة الوحوش مصنّفون لثلاث مجموعات
Those waiting for a chance to eat a smile fruit and gain beastly powers
أولئك الّذين أكلوا الفاكهة وينتظرون فرصة ...الحصول على قدرات حيوانيّة
are the Waiters!
"يُسمّون "الويترز
The strongest ones who hit the one-in-ten odds to gain bestial powers
والأقوياء الّذين اكتسبوا قدرات حيوانيّة ...من فرصة تقدّر بواحد من عشرة
are the Gifters!
"يسمّون "الغيفترز
Those warriors who ate a defective fruit and can only laugh
والمقاتلون الضّاحكون الّذين أكلوا ...الفاكهة ولم يكتسبوا أيّ قدرات
are the Pleasures!
"يُسمّون "البليجرز
What's worse, to mock the unfortunate ones who missed their chance at power,
ثمّ وكأنّهم يسخرون من المنحوسين الّذين لم يكتسبوا أيّ قدرات
they named the artificial fruit after seeing the negative outcome on those soldiers' faces...
سموا الفاكهة الاصطناعيّة تيمّنًا بتعابير أولئك الجنود
smile fruits!
سمايل" بمعنى ابتسامة"
I thought the name was strange, even if those devil fruits are artificial, but...
...حتّى إن كانت اصطناعيّة، طالما ظننت أنّه اسم غريب لفاكهة شيطان
the truth is just horrifying!
هذا فظيع
The tragedy goes even deeper!
تبدأ المأساة هناك
Orochi found the defective smile fruits with only a bite taken out of them.
لاحظ أوروتشي وجود فواكه "سمايل" الفاشلة الّتي سبق وقُضمت
Only the adverse side effects remained in these fruit,
إنّها ما زالت تحتوي على الأعراض الجانبيّة السيّئة
so they were able to make new Pleasures.
"أي أنّ باستطاعتهم إنتاج مزيدًا من "البليجرز
He didn't...!
...لا
In the town of leftovers outside the Flower Capital,
كان النّاس في بلدة أوكوبوري خارج عاصمة الزّهور يموتون ويبكون كلّ يوم جرّاء الجوع
Orochi had grown sick of it all,
فلم يُطق أوروتشي الأمر
so he mixed the failed smile fruits in with the leftovers from the capital.
لذلك خلط فواكه "سمايل" تلك مع مخلفات العاصمة
Look, apples! And they're still fresh!
إنّه تفّاح، ما زال طازجًا
There's enough for everyone! What a feast!
لنتشاركه جميعًا، سيكون رائعًا
It only took a few times until everyone knew...
بعد بضع مرّات في البداية كان لأيّ أحد أن يكتشف
exactly what the fruit was doing.
أيُّ الفواكه كانت
But still, these outcast townspeople...
...لكنّ سكّان البلدة
couldn't disobey their hunger pangs!
لم يستطيعوا كبح جوعهم
That is how Ebisu Town came to be a place where everyone is smiling and cheerful.
...وهكذا ظهرت بلدة إبيسو حيث الجميع يبتسمون ومرحون
At a glance, it looks so delightful,
البلدة المأساويّة حيث يبدو الجميع سعداء لكن يعجزون حتّى أن يتحسّروا على موت آبائهم
So...
...لذلك
please do not blame those who are laughing.
...لا تلمهم رجاءً... هؤلاء الضّاحكون
Amongst all the species, only humans can laugh!
من بين جميع الأجناس، وحدهم البشر بوسعهم الضّحك
Yeah!
نعم
♪ That's why you just gotta laugh! ♪
بما أن هذا صحيح فلمَ لا نضحك ونضحك؟
Daddy...
...أبي
Daddy!
أبي
This tragedy...
...كانت تلك
is Shogun Orochi's greatest sin...
من أثقل خطايا الشّوغن أوروتشي
He causes the people great misery...
...جعل البؤس يطغى على حياة النّاس
and even forbids them to grieve!
وحرمهم حتّى من الحزن
If this place...
...إن
is not hell...
...إن لم يكن هذا جحيمًا
then what is?!
فماذا يكون؟
Zorojuro!
زوروجورو-سان
This death suits you well, Yasuie!
مُت ميتة تناسبك يا ياسويي
How dare you live so brazenly in my country,
لا أصدّق مدى وقاحته بنجاته كلّ هذا الوقت في بلادي وانو
you impertinent hedgehog!
يا لوقاحتك أيّها القنفذ
Or should I say, you wretched rat!
كلاّ، بل يا جرذ المجاري
That's right, everyone!
هذا صحيح يا رفاق
Your former beloved daimyo of Hakumai, Shimotsuki Yasuie, has died!
شيموتسكي ياسويي، الدّايميو السّابق لهاكوماي الّذي أحببتموه قد مات
Send him to the other side with your howling laughter!
ودّعوه بأصوات ضحكاتكم
This is Wano! Bright and cheerful Wano!
هذه بلاد وانو، بلاد وانو البهيجة
It's practically heaven!
وكأنّها جنّة على الأرض
Laugh! Keep laughing!
اضحكوا، اضحكوا أكثر
Toko?
توكو؟
Toko!
توكو
No, Toko! Come back here!
كلاّ يا توكو، عودي
Daddy...
أبي
Daddy. Daddy.
أبي، أبي
I have some good medicine.
لديّ دواء جيّد
That's the girl from the soba stand!
...تلك الفتاة، أتت لأكل الصّوبا
Otoko!
أوتوكو-تشان
She must be Tonoyasu's daughter!
أعتقد أنّها ابنة تونوياسو
What?!
ماذا؟
Daddy, come back to me.
أبي، عد إليّ
This medicine will heal your wounds.
سيشفي هذا الدّواء جراحك
It's called toad oil and it works super well!
إنّه يُدعى زيت الضّفدع ومفعوله خارق
You'll be alright now.
...ستكون بخير
I'm so sorry, Otoko!
أعتذر يا أوتوكو
That medicine won't work!
...كلاّ، ذلك الدّواء
Hiyori!
هيوري-سان
Please, Toko! Come back!
رجاءً يا توكو، عودي
Daddy.
أبي
There you are, you little brat.
ها أنت أيّتها الشّقيّة
Clear the way!
ابتعدوا عن طريقي
I see. She's Yasuie's daughter!
فهمت... أنت ابنة ياسويي إذًا
No wonder she's so insolent!
يفسّر هذا سبب فظاظتك
If you...! If you...!
...لو أنّك... لو أنّك
If you...
...لو أنّك
hadn't laughed like an idiot that night...
لم تضحكي كالغبيّة حينها
Komurasaki would not have had to die!
لكانت كوموراساكي حيّة الآن
You little shit!
أيّتها القذرة
Daddy! Daddy!
أبي، أبي
Why you two...! Your family really knows how to piss me off!
تقودانني أنت ووالدك للجنون
Get up, Daddy!
عد إليّ يا أبي
I'll execute you, too!
سأعدمك
Die, you little shit!
موتي أيّتها القذرة
Otoko, run!
أوتوكو، اهربي
I do not want to lose you as well!
لا أريد أن أفقدك أنت أيضًا
Disappear from my sight!
اختفي من ناظريّ
Th-They're...
...هذان
Zorojuro the magistrate killer and Sangoro the soba cook!
زوروجورو قاتل القاضي وطبّاخ الصّوبا سانغورو
Those idiots have gone and done it now...!
هما... عرفتُ أنّهما لن يكبحا نفسيهما
This will be trouble.
سنواجه مشكلات بسبب هذا
But we can't really blame them!
لكن لا يمكننا أن نلومهما
Yeah, I'm glad they swooped in to save Otoko.
نعم، أبليا حسنًا بإنقاذ أوتوكو
Damn you for interfering with the execution!
كيف تجرؤان على التدّخل في إعدامها؟
The rat and his pack keep coming out of the woodwork, huh?!
ظهر مزيدٌ من رفاق الجرذ
Yasuie's brat of a daughter committed a grave crime!
ابنة ياسويي... تلك الشّقيّة اللّعينة مجرمة خطيرة
Hey, samurai! You have my permission to kill anyone who interferes with the execution!
أيّها السّاموراي، انطلقوا واقتلوا !كلّ من تدخّل في الإعدام
– Yes, my lord!
حاضر
Hey, are those guns pointed at us?!
مهلًا، أليسوا يصوّبون بأسلحتهم نحونا؟
Oh no!
مصيبة
Run, you fools!
اهربوا يا أغبياء
Cut them down!
نالوا منهم
Sorry, but I don't have time for you.
اعذرني فلا وقت لدي من أجلك
And neither do I!
ولا أنا
Then get the hell outta here, Browgoro!
اغرب عن وجهي إذًا أيّها الحاجب-غورو
Browgoro?
الحاجب-غورو"؟"
It's Sangoro!
إني سانغورو
You get the hell outta here, Mossjuro!
اغرب أنت أيها الطحلب-جورو
Mossjuro?!
الطحلب-جورو"؟"
You've got that moss-ball head!
شعرك يبدو ككرة طحلب
What'd you say?!
ماذا؟
Should I slice you up before Orochi does?!
أتريدني أن أقطّعك قبل أوروتشي؟
Shut up! Then I'll put my foot up your ass before Kaido does!
اخرس، سأركلك إذًا حتّى الموت قبل كايدو
You want some?!
ما الّذي قلته؟
Daddy!
أبي
Otoko, you're safe!
أوتوكو... حمدًا أنّها بخير
Is he Zorojuro's friend?
هل هو... رفيق زوروجورو-سان؟
Roronoa Zoro of the Straw Hat Pirates.
...رورونوا زورو من قراصنة قبّعة القشّ، والآخر هو
Vinsmoke Sanji...
فينسموك سانجي
The Straw Hat Pirates have gathered in Wano after all.
...إذًا فقراصنة قبّعة القشّ هنا في بلاد وانو حقًّا
Even so, I'm surprised by how brazenly they appeared.
لا أصدّق أنّهم أظهروا وجوههم بكلّ وقاحة هكذا
Hey!
أنتما
Do you have a problem with how brazen we are?!
ألديكما مشكلة بطريقة ظهورنا؟
Yeah, do you?! Also...
...نعم، ألديكما؟ وأيضًا
don't ever address me as Vinsmoke! Got it?!
إيّاك أن تناديني بفينسموك، مفهوم؟
Then let's finish this right here!
حسنًا، سأنهي أمرك فحسب
Fire!
أطلقوا
That damn ronin...
...ذلك الرّونين اللّعين
Ready!
ليستعدّ التّالون
Fire!
أطلقوا
Just get Otoko out of here already!
خذ أوتوكو واهرب بسرعة
No, not yet!
لا، ليس بعد
He's mine...!
...عليه أن
He's cocky for a rat!
يتصرّف ذلك الجرذ بقلّة أدب
Take care of her!
اعتنِ بها
What?! W-Wait!
ماذا؟ مـ-مهلًا
He's attacking?!
هل سيهاجم؟
Charge! Engage him!
قاتلوه، قاتلوه
That ronin is coming for me!
سيهاجمني ذلك الرّونين
Run, Browgoro!
اهرب أيّها الحاجب-غورو
Know your place and mind your manners, you lowly bastard!
كيف يعقل أن يكون ذلك المواطن الدّنيء فظًّا هكذا؟
It's up to me to cut you down!
عليّ أن أقطعك بنفسي
Hey, Moss Head! Don't charge in without backup!
أيها الطحلبي، لا تتهوّر بدخول قتال وحدك
Ready your arms!
استعدّوا للإطلاق
Uh-oh!
سُحقًا
Fire!
أطلقوا
Stop already, you idiot!
مهلًا، توقّف أيّها الغبيّ
What did Tonoyasu die for?!
من أجل ماذا ضحّى تونوياسو بنفسه؟
Whoa, wait a minute, mister!
مهلًا، انتظر قليلًا يا سيدي اليافع
We live our lives on the cusp of evens and odds, just as with good and evil.
كما يقال، هنالك مَساوٍ وخلافات في هذا العالم لكنّ الخير والشّرّ يتواليان
Let's put an end to this here!
لنضع حدًّا لهذا ها هنا
Okay?!
مفهوم؟
In this country, we call everyone's smiling face
...في هذه البلاد، نسمّي وجوه الجميع المبتسمة
an "Ebisu grin," mister!
إبيسو غاو" يا سيّدي"
That's why this place is called Ebisu!
لهذا السّبب تُسمّى بلدة إبيسو
We won't let poverty get us down!
لن يُحبطنا الفقر
Yasu...
...ياسو
Could he be one of the Red Scabbards' men?
هل يعقل أنّه من جنود الأغماد؟
Hey! Protect me, samurai!
هيّا أيّها السّاموراي، احموني
Seven-Twenty-Pound Phoenix!
ناناهيكو نيجو باوند هو
Who is that man?!
من ذلك الرّجل؟
Boss Kyoshiro...
...الزّعيم كيوشيرو
My lord, you are too careless.
كم أنت متهوّر يا سيدي
You should not have come to the execution with such a meager escort.
لا يجدر بك المجيء إلى ساحة الإعدام بحراسة ضعيفة كهذه
But... that ronin...
...ذلك الرّونين
truly intended to kill me.
كان يسعى لقتلي حقًّا
Hey, Moss Head! What the hell do you think you're doing?!
أيها الطحلبي، بماذا تفكّر؟
Cool your head!
هدّئ من روعك
X Drake Ancient Saur-Saur Fruit: Allosaurus
ديس دريك فاكهة التّنّين، صنف الألوصور
A surprise attack from that monster?!
هجوم مفاجئ من شخص ضخم كهذا؟
Take this!
خذ هذه
Ready your fire!
استعدّوا للإطلاق
Well, well, well... Verily, this scene will become a bloodbath...
عجبًا، سيصبح هذا مشهدًا لسفك الدّماء يقينًا
What should we do? Just stand here and watch?!
ماذا علينا أن نفعل؟ هل سنقف هنا ونشاهد فحسب؟
There's no point in staying out of the fight now!
بما أنّ الأمر آل لهذا، فعلينا القتال أيضًا
Hold it! That would ruin the whole operation!
مهلًا لحظة، سيفسد هذا خطّتنا بالكامل
And if we get involved, we'll no longer be welcome in the capital.
وإن تورّطنا في هذا فلن نستطيع البقاء في العاصمة
Be that as it may, we cannot let them desecrate Lord Yasuie's body!
رغم ذلك، لا يجب أن نسمح لهم بتعريض جثّة ياسويي-ساما للعموم
We have to carry him away somehow!
علينا أخذها بطريقة ما
That may be true, but...
...معك حقّ، ولكن
Let's split up. Where should we rendezvous?
لننفصل، أين علينا أن نلتقي؟
I'll join you in the fight!
سأساعد في القتال أيضًا
No, wait! Now is not the time for anyone associated with Lord Oden to be seen here!
لا، تمهّلوا، هذا ليس الوقت المناسب ليظهر حلفاء أودين-ساما أنفسهم
That's right. You two need to slip away without getting seen.
هذا صحيح، اسبقانا أنتما يا شينوبو-تشان وكنجورو خلسة
But...
...لكن
We're the ones who started this, so we'll take care of it ourselves.
عضوا طاقمنا هما من خلّف هذه الفوضى، لذلك سنهتمّ بها نحن
We cannot thank you enough.
شكرًا لكم
We must go, Shinobu. Leave this to Lady Onami.
هيّا بنا يا شينوبو، لندع الأمر لأونامي-دونو
Take the lord shogun to the castle.
خذوا جلالة الشّوغن إلى القلعة
You know what to do! Kill them!
اسمع، اقتلهم
Kill anyone who stands against me!
اقتل كلّ واحد ممّن تمرّدوا ضدّي
He's not getting away!
لن أسمح له بالهرب
Fire!
أطلقوا
Cover me!
أعتمد عليك
Alright!
حسنًا
Bulletproof?!
أهو مضادّ للرّصاص؟
What's up with that carpenter?!
ما قصّة ذلك النجّار؟
Strong Right!
سترونغ رايت
Who are they?!
من يكونون؟
Who the hell are these guys?!
من يكونون يا ترى؟
Oh, there he is!
مهلًا، ها هو هناك
Ah! He took Lord Yasuie!
كلاّ، سرق جثّة ياسويي-ساما
What in the world is happening?!
ما الّذي يحدث هنا؟
Don't worry! I won't let them desecrate his body!
لا تقلق، لن أسمح لهم بتدنيس جثّته
Oh no!
كلاّ
Is that...?!
أهذا...؟
Oh, Usohachi! Thanks, you're a lifesaver!
نعم، شكرًا يا أوسوهاتشي، أنقذتني
He's atop that ladder! Bring him down!
فوق ذلك السلّم، صوّبوا
Hey now, it's just too ironic if the sniper gets sniped!
مهلًا، مهلًا، إنّ تعرّض قنّاص للقنص فيه سخرية
Mil Fleurs:
ميل فلور
Gigantesco Mano Spank!
غيغانتسكو مانو سبانك
Thanks for the help, Orobi!
شكرًا يا أوروبي
And another one of them?
ظهرت واحدة أخرى من رفاقهم
That woman... is the geisha from before! I knew she was a sorceress!
...إنّها
The enemy is formidable! Surround them!
الأعداء أقوياء، حاصروهم
Onami!
أونامي
Leave them to me!
دعي أمرهم لي
Thunderbolt Tempo!
ثندربولت تيمبو
Outta my way!
ابتعد عن طريقي
I think not!
لن أفعل
In that case...
...إذًا
taste steel!
سأقطعك
I am the shogun's dog.
أنا كلب الشّوغن
Poêle à Frire: Spectre!
تقنية المقلاة: الطّيف بويله فرير سبكتر
Let's wrap this up and get the hell outta here!
لننتهِ من هذا الأمر ونغادر المكان
Yeah!
حاضر
Lethal Atlas Comet!
مذنب أطلس الفتاك هيساتسو أطلس سيسيه
Mil Fleurs: Gigantesco Mano!
ألف زهرة: اليد العملاقة ميل فلور غيغانتسكو مانو
Weapons Left!
سلاح اليد اليسرى ويبنز ليفت
Tornado Tempo!
جوّ الزّوبعة تورنيدو تيمبو
All troops, attack! Charge!
إلى كلّ الجنود! قاتلوهم! قاتلوهم
Rebels are rioting in Rasetsu Town!
يثير المتمرّدون الشّغب في بلدة راسيتسو
By order of the shogun, these criminals are wanted dead or alive!
حسب أمر الشّوغن، لا يهمّ إن أمسكناهم أحياء أم أمواتًا
Kill them if you have to!
لا تتردّدوا في قتلهم
Let's go, you guys!
انطلقوا يا رفاق
Kick their asses!
أوسعوهم ضربًا
Say, Sir Straw Hat...
أحسنتم
That's it!
أخبرني يا فتى قبعة القش
Huh?
أهؤلاء الّذين يظهرون على حلزون لفيفة الضّوء هم رفاقك؟
Huh? That's right. I was told to keep it a secret.
...أظنّ أنّه قيل لي أن أبقي الأمر سرًّا
But I don't really care.
...لكن من يهتمّ
Let's go!
انطلقوا
Get in there! You got this! Get 'em!
!هناك! هيّا، هيّا! أطيحوا بهم
This can't be good.
...هذا سيئ
Zorojuro! Keep it up!
زوروجورو، أنت لها
Hey, Straw Hat!
يا قبّعة القشّ
Is that green-haired guy with you?
هل أخضر الشّعر ذاك صاحبك؟
Isn't that Zorojuro, the vile criminal who killed a magistrate?
ذلك هو زوروجورو، المجرم الخطير الّذي قتل القاضي، صحيح؟
What a riot! Of all people, he's gunning for Orochi!
يا للإثارة، إنه يقصد قتل أوروتشي
What is it, Babanuki? It's just getting good. Come back later.
ما بك يا بابانوكي؟ الوضع يزداد حماسًا، إن أمرك يمكنه الانتظار
But a criminal has just arrived from the Flower Capital...
...لكنّ هنالك مجرم وصل توًّا من عاصمة الزّهور
From the Flower Capital? Who could it be at a time like this?
من عاصمة الزّهور؟ من أتى الآن؟
He should arrive momentarily.
سيصل المجرم قريبًا
Right through that gate.
من خلال تلك البوّابة
Manslayer
هيتوكيري
Vile Criminal
مجرم خطير
Who's that?
من هذا؟
This useless trash failed the mission assigned to him by the shogun a the Flower Capital.
إنّه الحثالة عديم النّفع الّذي لم يستطع إنجاز مهمّة أوكلها له الشّوغن في عاصمة الزّهور
Lord Orochi said to punish him however we see fit!
لدينا رسالة من أوروتشي-ساما يقول فيها أنّ بإمكانكم معاقبته كما تشاؤون
We present Kamazo the Reaper!
أحضرنا هيتوكيري كامازو
So, you're that Kamazo I've heard so much about, huh?!
أنت هو كامازو إذًا... سمعت الكثير عنك
And there's one more!
وهنالك واحد آخر
Stop right there.
توقّف الآن
Here is my report:
لديّ تقرير
While we were escorting Kamazo here, we caught another criminal!
بينما كنّا نصطحب كامازو إلى هنا، أمسكنا بحثالة آخر
The escapee, Captain Kid!
كابتن كيد الهارب
Jaggy!
المسنّن
This scum was shouting something as he approached us,
هذا الحثالة اقترب منا وهو يصرخ شيئا ما
so I put a few rounds in him.
لذلك أطلقت عليه بضع مرّات لكنّه لم يحاول حتّى الهرب وها نحن هنا
I guess he forgot he's wearing seastone cuffs!
ربّما نسي أنّه مكبّل بأصفاد الحجر البحري
Kid! What, is your head full of rocks?!
كيد، يا لك من مغفّل
He got away clean, so why did he get himself caught?!
لقد تكبّد عناء الهرب فلماذا قد يسلّم نفسه؟
Hey, stop!
توقّف
I said stop!
قلت لك توقّف
You used to say you hate the way you laugh...
...أتذكّر كيف أنّك لا تحبّ ضحكتك تلك
At some point, you even quit laughing out loud entirely!
...حتّى أنّك توقّفت عن الضّحك بصوت عالٍ في مرحلةٍ
Weren't you the guy who beat anyone half to death who mocked the way you laughed?!
وكلّ من كان يسخر من ضحكتك كان يتعرّض لضرب مبرح على يديك
So just... stop it already...
...أرجوك... توقّف
And then, you began to wear a mask to hide your face...
...بدأت ترتدي القناع لإخفاء وجهك في مرحلةٍ
That's the person I knew...
...وهذا ما أعرفه عنك
What the hell happened to you?!
فما الّذي جرى لك؟
After we got separated, what did Kaido do to you?!
ما الّذي فعله بك كايدو بعد انفصالنا؟
Or was it Orochi who got to you?! Where's everyone else?!
أم أنّ أوروتشي فعل بك شيئًا؟ وأين البقيّة؟
Answer me!
أجبني
C'mon, answer me...!
أجبني... أجبني أرجوك
Killer!
يا كيلر
What?! That's him?!
ماذا؟ أذاك هو؟
That's the masked guy who was with Jaggy?
هل ذلك هو الرّجل المقنّع الّذي كان مع المسنّن؟
Jaggy must've tried to save him...
لا بدّ أنّ المسنّن حاول إنقاذه
How cruel...
...يا للقسوة
Forced to eat a smile fruit,
لقد أُجبر على أكل فاكهة سمايل ومُنح قناع ضحكٍ لا يستطيع خلعه أبدًا
That bastard Orochi does unspeakable things...
ذلك اللّعين أوروتشي، يا لقسوته
What did they do to you to change you so much?!
ما الّذي فعلوه ليغيّروك بالكامل هكذا؟
Who did this to my partner?!
من فعل هذا بصاحبي؟
Where is my crew?!
أين هو طاقمي؟
Dammit!
سُحقًا
Don't screw with me!
لا تعبث معي
Damn you!
...أيّها الـ
You got something to say to me?
هل لديك مشكلة؟
That's right. I thought up a fun game.
نعم، فكّرت في لعبة شيّقة
Sorry to keep you waiting, you sons of bitches!
شكرًا على الانتظار أيّها الحمقى
The Sumo Inferno...
...نزالات سومو الجحيم
is back on!
ستُستأنف
However, there's a new rule.
لكن لدينا قاعدة جديدة
The blades in your collars kill you the moment you step out of this ring.
إن خطوتما خارج الحلبة ستُقتلان بمسامير الأطواق
That rule hasn't changed.
وهذا لم يتغيّر
But the new rule is...
...لكنّ القاعدة الجديدة
as long as you guys are alive, those two will be submerged in the water.
ما دمتما على قيد الحياة فسيظلّ هذان مغطّسين في الماء
In other words, as soon as you and the geezer...
...ممّا يعني أنّه فقط عندما ستتذوّقان أنت وذلك العجوز
are dead as door nails...
طعم الموت
we'll pull those two out of the water.
سنخرجهما من الماء
That's just dumb! I've got nothing to do with them!
هذه سخافة، لا علاقة لهم بي
Oh, I know.
...نعم، هذا صحيح على الأرجح
why has this rule made you upset?
ولكن، لماذا تبدو مستاءً قليلًا من ذلك؟
Is it because you two are rivals from the same generation?
هل السّبب هو أنّكم متنافسون من نفس الجيل؟
If that's the case, then just sacrifice yourself for them right away.
حسنًا، بإمكانكما دائمًا التّضحية بحياتكما من أجلهما في الحال
Notoriety and bounties worth hundreds of millions of berries mean squat...
بغضّ النّظر عن مدى شهرتكم أو كم من مئات الملايين من البيري بلغت مكافآتكم
when all humans...
...فكلّ البشر
drown in just five centimeters of water.
سيغرقون ولو في خمسة سنتيمترات من الماء
Let the game begin!
والآن، لتبدأ اللّعبة
If that's how it is...
في تلك الحالة
join me in the ring!
!فلتدخل أنت الحلبة إذًا
I'll kick your ass and end this!
سأوسعك ضربًا وأنهي هذا
Who do you think you're talking to?
إلى من تتكلّم في رأيك؟
Don't get cocky...
لا تستفزّني
you little punk!
أوغاد
Sir Straw Hat!
يا فتى قبّعة القشّ
Hey.
أنت
Punk.
يا شقيّ
What possesses you to cling to hope the way you do?
لا أفهم تفاؤلك هذا
Do you really think you'll make it out of here alive?
أتحسب فعلًا أنّ بإمكانك الخروج من هنا حيًّا؟
You think you can beat us?
أتحسب أنّ بإمكانك هزيمتنا؟
You are all going to die!
الموت هو مصيركم يا حمقى
One by one!
الواحد تلو الآخر
Shut the hell up!
اخرس
I die...
...إن مكان مماتي
where I choose!
سيكون من اختياري
Hey, what's that sound?!
أنت، ما هذا الصّوت؟
Hey, what's wrong?!
أجبني، ما الخطب؟
Hey! Come in already!
هيّا، أجيبوني
Queen, Your Awesomeness, we lost contact with the gate guards!
كوين-ساما، فقدنا الاتّصال بالحرس في الخارج
I finally made it.
وصلتُ أخيرًا
Oshiruko!
يا أوشيروكو